SHAHID KHAN

HTML/EMAIL DEVELOPER



+923355770766

develhubb@gmail.com

Dhamial Camp Ahmad Abad

www.github.com/Develhubs

PROFILE

Hello, I'm Shahid Khan and I'm a freelancer HTML Email Developer. I've been making HTML Emails for 3 years, which helps HTML Email Developing Business. I am a Developer who is constantly increasing my technical knowledge and skills.

I'm a passionate, result -based developer that creates and examining accountable emails and landing pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I'm also going to solve a problem that is permanently working to improve my coding skills.

SKILLS

- Web Designing
- Design Thinking
- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- MJML
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- SEO
- JavaScript
- Python
- WordPress
- Shopify
- Amazon FBA
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Allama Iqbal Open University

Undergraduate

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Amazon KDP

2017 - Present

- Designing E-book, and Journal
- Designing School Notebook
- Designing Color Notebook

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Etsy

2017 - Present

- Designing Digital Products
- T-Shirts Designing
- Designing Wedding Cards, and Stickers

EMAIL TEMPLETE DEVELOPMENT

Freelancer

2020 - Present

Build and test email templates using HTML tables, inline CSS, and Stripo.

- Transactional Email Template
- Newsletter Email Template
- Promotional Email Template
- Landing Page